Frances Ryan Thomas
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Frances Ryan Thomas
2.1.3.3.2
Marist College
  Box 1520
- Frances Ryan Thomas, 2.1.3.3.2
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan [Thomas] (infant and toddler photographs), circa 1894 - 1899; 9 (Box 1520)
    - Frances [as a toddler], 1
    - Verso: Frances [as a toddler], 1-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas as a toddler], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas as a toddler], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas as a toddler], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas as a toddler], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas as a toddler], 6
    - Frances Ryan (Mrs. Lowell Thomas) when a baby, 7
    - Verso: Frances Ryan (Mrs. Lowell Thomas) when a baby, 7-verso
    - Norman - Phillip - and Francis [sic] [Ryan], 8
    - Verso: Norman - Phillip - and Francis [sic] [Ryan], 8-verso
    - Norman Andrew Ryan; Francis [sic] Laura Ryan; coming home from church, 9
    - Verso: Norman Andrew Ryan; Francis [sic] Laura Ryan; coming home from church, 9-verso
    - Caption: Frances [Frances Ryan Thomas as a toddler], 10
    - Caption: Frances [reverse side of 9.11] [Frances Ryan Thomas as a toddler], 11
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), circa 1900; 10 (Box 1520)
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 1
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 2
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 3
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 4
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 5
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 6
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 7
    - Verso: Mrs. H. P. Ryan 1414 Clayton St., 7-verso
    - Frances Ryan [Thomas] (childhood portrait), 8
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan Thomas (dogs), circa 1930s - 1950s; 11 (Box 1520)
    - Family dogs [Young Frances Ryan Thomas with dogs], 1
    - Family dogs [Young Frances Ryan Thomas with dogs], 2
    - Family dogs [Young Frances Ryan Thomas with dogs], 3
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. sitting inside with two dogs], 4
    - Family dogs [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas, outside with small dog], 5
    - Family dogs [2 copies] [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas, outside with small dog], 6
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas holding a dog, sitting on porch with another woman who is holding a dog. Large dog, lying behind them], 7
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas? Out in garden with dog], 8
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas? Sitting outside with dogs], 9
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas walking down stairs, outside with a dog., 10
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas holding dog outside on a wooden table], 11
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas kneeling on ground with dog], 12
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on chair outside, petting dog], 13
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on chair outside, petting dog], 14
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside with dog], 15
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on porch with two dogs in her lap and another dog lying at her feet], 16
    - Family dogs [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on porch with two dogs in her lap and another dog lying at her feet], 17
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan [Thomas] (portraits), circa 1910s; 12 (Box 1520)
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 1
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 2
    - Verso: Frances Ryan Thomas, 2-verso
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 3
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 4
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 5
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 6
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 7
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 8
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 9
    - Verso: Mrs. Lowell Thomas, 2 cols[?] today MUST with locklont[?] story 7 1/2 each[?], 9-verso
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 10
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 11
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 12
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 13
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 14
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 15
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan [Thomas], 16
    - Note: Photographer label, 17
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan Thomas (portraits), circa 1920s - 1930s; 13 (Box 1520)
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas [Colored photo], 1
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas [Colored photo], 2
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 3
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 4
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 5
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 6
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 7
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 8
    - Verso: newspaper clipping, 8-verso
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 9
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 10
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan Thomas (portraits), circa 1940s - 1960s; 14 (Box 1520)
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 1
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 2
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 3
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 4
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 5
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 6
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 7
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 8
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 9
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 10
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 11
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 12
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 13
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 14
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 15
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 16
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 17
    - Portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas, 18
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan [Thomas], circa early 1900s - 1915; 15 (Box 1520)
    - When I was a freshman [Frances Ryan Thomas with two men and another woman], 1
    - Verso: When I was a freshman, 1-verso
    - [Young Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside, wearing hat], 2
    - [Young Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside, wearing hat], 3
    - [Young Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside, wearing hat], 4
    - [Young Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside, wearing hat], 5
    - [Young Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside by waterfall], 6
    - [Young Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside by flower bushes], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing on steps], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing on steps], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on grass with man], 10
    - [France Ryan Thomas sitting on rocks near flag with man. ], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on rocks near flag with man and woman], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on rocks near flag with man and woman], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas? Walking on dirt road with a man], 14
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas? Walking on dirt road with a man], 15
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas? With another woman, outside near trees], 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas? With another woman, outside near trees], 17
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on rocks with a boy, eating fruit], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on rocks with a boy, eating fruit], 19
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas? With group of people sitting around a bonfire], 20
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on rocks near rushing water], 21
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas? With group of people in vehicle on bridge], 22
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing near pine tree], 23
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing near pine tree], 24
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a car outside of a mansion], 25
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a car outside of a mansion], 26
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at desk with map of the United States behind her], 27
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at desk with map of the United States behind her], 28
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with a group of people], 29
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with a group of people], 30
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas wearing cap and gown for graduation, standing with a group of girls also wearing caps and gowns], 31
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with a woman and three men], 32
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with a woman and three men], 33
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with a woman and three men], 34
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan Thomas [includes 1 color photograph], circa 1920 - 1960s; 16 (Box 1520)
    - Frances with Dan Edwards, 1
    - Verso: Frances with Dan Edwards, 1-verso
    - Dressed for a costume ball on a steamer sailing down the Red Sea. On the left, Mrs. Lowell Thomas, disguised as a member of an oriental harem. Next to her an Australian girl representing Uncle Sam; the wild-looking warrior sitting in the middle is Squadron Leader Peter Drummond, Australian flying ace in the Palestine campaign, and today one of the higher ranking officers of the Royal Air Force. The dark-looking sheik on the right is not Othello. He is a Scotchman, Lieutenant McCall McCowan, an officer of the famous Black Watch [circa 1920], 2
    - Note: Dressed for a costume ball on a steamer sailing down the Red Sea. On the left, Mrs. Lowell Thomas, disguised as a member of an oriental harem. Next to her an Australian girl representing Uncle Sam; the wild-looking warrior sitting in the middle is Squadron Leader Peter Drummond, Australian flying ace in the Palestine campaign, and today one of the higher ranking officers of the Royal Air Force. The dark-looking sheik on the right is not Othello. He is a Scotchman, Lieutenant McCall McCowan, an officer of the famous Black Watch [circa 1920], 3
    - [Dressed for a costume ball on a steamer sailing down the Red Sea. On the left, Mrs. Lowell Thomas, disguised as a member of an oriental harem. Next to her an Australian girl representing Uncle Sam; the wild-looking warrior sitting in the middle is Squadron Leader Peter Drummond, Australian flying ace in the Palestine campaign, and today one of the higher ranking officers of the Royal Air Force. The dark-looking sheik on the right is not Othello. He is a Scotchman, Lieutenant McCall McCowan, an officer of the famous Black Watch [circa 1920]], 4
    - The costume I wore at the fancy dress ball on board the S.S. Orvieto. It is purple and gold [Frances Ryan Thomas], 5
    - Verso: The costume I wore at the fancy dress ball on board the S.S. Orvieto. It is purple and gold, 5-verso
    - [The costume I wore at the fancy dress ball on board the S.S. Orvieto. It is purple and gold (Frances Ryan Thomas)], 6
    - Sam Pryor, Will Hays, [Mrs. Frances Ryan] Thomas, [President Herbert] Hoover, Mrs. Will Hays, 7
    - Verso: Sam Pryor, Will Hays, [Mrs. Frances Ryan] Thomas, [President Herbert] Hoover, Mrs. Will Hays, 7-verso
    - Fran [(Frances Ryan Thomas)] - barnstorming Europe, 8
    - Verso: Fran - barnstorming Europe, 8-verso
    - Fran [(Frances Ryan Thomas)] - barnstorming Europe, 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas mounted on horse], 10
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas mounted on horse], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas mounted on horse], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing by bushes, smiling], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas holding hands with another woman], 14
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with a woman in front of bushes, smiling for picture], 15
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting among a crowd of people], 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting among a crowd of people], 17
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing in front of world map], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing and smiling], 19
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas on chair with dog and another woman seated next to her], 20
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing behind flowers], 21
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas seated outside on chair], 22
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 23
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 24
    - 1949? [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 25
    - Verso: 1949?, 25-verso
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 26
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 27
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 28
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 29
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 30
    - [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas smiling], 31
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas wearing a hat, standing on steps], 32
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at table, pouring tea], 33
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at table, pouring tea], 34
    - [(Colored photo) Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on couch], 35
  Box 1521
- Frances Ryan Thomas, 2.1.3.3.2
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan Thomas, circa 1930s - 1940s; 1 (Box 1521)
    - Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 1
    - Verso: Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 1-verso
    - Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 2
    - Verso: Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 2-verso
    - Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 3
    - Verso: Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 3-verso
    - Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 4
    - Verso: Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 4-verso
    - Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 5
    - Verso: Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 5-verso
    - Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 6
    - Verso: Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 6-verso
    - Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 7
    - Verso: Mrs. T. alone; 1931 or 1932, 7-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at table], 8
    - August 18 1939 [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting down, holding a tray], 9
    - Verso: August 18 1939, 9-verso
    - Fran and Mrs. Thornburg, 10
    - Verso: Fran and Mrs. Thornburg, 10-verso
    - Fran and Mrs. Thornburg, 11
    - Verso: Fran and Mrs. Thornburg, 11-verso
    - Fran and Mrs. Thornburg, 12
    - Verso: Fran and Mrs. Thornburg, 12-verso
    - Mrs. Thornburg and daughter in late 1940s, 13
    - Verso: Mrs. Thornburg and daughter in late 1940s, 13-verso
    - Fran, Mrs. Thornburg and daughter, 14
    - Verso: Fran, Mrs. Thornburg and daughter, 14-verso
    - Fran, Mrs. Thornburg and daughter, 15
    - Verso: Fran, Mrs. Thornburg and daughter, 15-verso
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Frances Ryan Thomas and mother, Eunice Ryan, circa 1910 - 1940s; 2 (Box 1521)
    - [Woman sitting with an older woman (Frances Ryan Thomas sitting with Eunice Ryan?)], 1
    - [Woman standing oustide (Eunice Ryan?)], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on porch with dog and another woman (Eunice Ryan?)], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas leaning against opened car door with a woman sitting inside of the vehicle (Eunice Ryan)], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing in front of car with a woman inside (Eunice Ryan?)], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with another woman (Eunice Ryan?)], 6
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Friends and family, circa early 1900s - 1915; 3 (Box 1521)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of people seated around table], 1
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of people seated around table], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of people sitting on front porch], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man wearing baseball uniform], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man sitting at desk], 5
    - [Flowers in vase], 6
    - [Grand building in the distance (faded photo)], 7
    - [Small house surrouned by pine trees], 8
    - [Lake with trees at the left, corner of house caught in picture], 9
    - [Field with house in distance], 10
    - [View of grand building], 11
    - [Top of tree], 12
    - [Pool for a fountain], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: People standing in front of mansion], 14
    - [View of house on street], 15
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Little girl sitting and hugging a baby], 16
    - [View of pillars and fountain in distance], 17
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Little girl hugging a dog], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man playing tennis], 19
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Baby in stroller in front of bushes], 20
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Baby in bouncer in front of stairs], 21
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Three men standing in front of trees], 22
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man standing in front of uprooted tree], 23
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man walking down a dirt road lined with trees], 24
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man standing on rock], 25
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man sitting], 26
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Friends and family, circa early 1900s - 1915; 4 (Box 1521)
    - [View of large building with crowd of people walking toward the doors], 1
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Crowd of people outside], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Girls dressed in light dresses, holding hands in a circle], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of people seated at dining table], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman sitting], 5
    - Verso: [Illegible], 5-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman standing with her arms crossed], 6
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two boys], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two men wearing lab aprons], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Girl wearing a dress, posing], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Girl wearing a dress, posing], 10
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Girl playing a violin], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Boy sitting on rocks], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and famly: Man and woman sitting on rocks], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Three people sitting on a rock], 14
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman standing], 15
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man on a swing, four other people standing behind him], 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of people sitting by a tree], 17
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man sitting on steps], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman on steps], 19
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man in suit, with hands on hips], 20
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman standing next to car], 21
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two women sitting on rocks], 22
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of women posing for a picture], 23
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of women posing for a picture], 24
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of women on rocks], 25
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of women on rocks], 26
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Men in a pyramid formation], 27
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two people looking out from behind trees, under a sign that reads "DamfinoVI" (?)], 28
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man with a little girl riding a donkey underneath a sign that reads "DamfinoVI"], 29
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man with a little girl riding a donkey underneath a sign that reads "DamfinoVI"], 30
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man standing next to large ball], 31
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of men lifting large ball], 32
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of men lifting large ball], 33
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Crowd of people on football field], 34
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: People playing on football field], 35
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: People playing on football field], 36
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: People playing on football field], 37
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Friends and family, circa early 1900s - 1915; 5 (Box 1521)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of men and women sitting on stairs], 1
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Pillars and fountains in the distance], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Dirt road lined with trees], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Close-up of woman], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman standing on a snowy sidewalk], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: People riding in a horse-drawn carraige], 6
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man on rock looking out], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Fountain], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man standing outside of building], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two men and a woman sitting on side of house], 10
    - Verso: KAR[?] Frank Dunth Stems [?], Allen Deattie, 10-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Blurry picture of woman], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Child sitting on stone wall], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: People riding in a horse-drawn carraige], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman sitting on rocks], 14
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: House], 15
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Running water], 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Lake], 17
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman sitting outside with two children], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two formally dressed women holding suitcases], 19
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Little boy standing outside of house], 20
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman standing among tall grass], 21
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman sitting outside with two children], 22
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman outside of house with dog and little boy], 23
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman and man standing], 24
    - Verso: J & P, 24-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman on porch], 25
    - Verso: AB, 25-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman and man standing on porch] Jannette Beattie and KAR [?], 26
    - Verso: Jannette Beattie and KAR [?], 26-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman walking by side of house] Running away from the Kodak. Aleen Beattie, 27
    - Verso: [Running away from the Kodak. Aleen Beattie], 27-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Snow covered neighborhood] Taken from our back porch, 28
    - Verso: Taken from our back porch, 28-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man standing on porch] NAR(?), 29
    - Verso: NAR(?), 29-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of children in doorway], 30
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Three children and dog outside of house], 31
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman standing on porch] Smith & Jaunet Beattie (sister) [Jannet?], 32
    - Verso: Smith & Jaunet Beattie (sister) [Jannet?], 32-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman standing on dirt road], 33
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Three women standing on porch], 34
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman [Francis Ryan Thomas?] standing outside snowy house], 35
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman in hat and coat standing on balcony], 36
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman in hat and coat leaning against brick wall], 37
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Pine tree at right and white building in distance], 38
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman [Francis Ryan Thomas?] wearing coat and hat], 39
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of people sitting on porch steps for picture], 40
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman climbing rocks at stream], 41
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Baby doll standing on wall], 42
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman climbing rocks at stream], 43
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Rushing water], 44